CHRIS POTURALSKI

REAL ESTATE AGENT

CONTACT

Phone 317-709-0689

E-mail chrispotural@gmail.com

• Address
Irvine, CA

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree Of Liberal Arts

Indiana University 2015-2019

Minor Degree in Psychology Minor Degree in

Criminal Justice

SKILLS

Excellent Customer Service

Food Safety Practices

Communication

Problem Solving

Time Managment

Teamwork

PROFILE

A current real estate agent with 6+ years experience in sales 3+ years in marketing. Before my current profession, I have had work experience in multiple restaurants starting with bussing, cooking, serving, and bartending experience. After graduating, I re-located to Irvine, CA to pursue a career in residential real estate sales to build upon my sales experience and also to gain marketing experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

REAL ESTATE AGENT

First Team Real Estate & Anvil Real Estate | 2019-Current

- Actively prospect and find new clients to buy, sell, or lease property in Orange County, CA.
- Draft up contracts to purchase, sell, or lease property.
- Promote property through online advertisements, open house, MLS, and other online platforms.
- Use data and negotiation skills to obtain to complete a transaction.
- · Brand products and services on social media
- Communicate effectively with both sides of the transaction to ensure all timelines are met and consumers are satisfied.

SERVER & BARTENDER

Scotty's Brewhouse | 2018-2019

- Recorded food and beverage orders and served customer requests to high standards.
- Maintained full product knowledge or menu and specials.
- Ability to recommend and pair products upon customer preferences.
- Establish customer relationships to ensure customers enjoy and want to come back to the restaurant.
- Prepare and deliver high quality cocktails for an entire restaurant while maintaining bar top and tables.
- As lead server, guide servers to ensure inventory is stocked, restaurant is cleaned, and assist servers when needed.